Now, this might be
the room of any small boy,
but it happens to belong to
a boy named Christopher Robin.
And, like most small boys,
Christopher Robin
had toy animals to play with.
And, together, they had many
remarkable adventures
in an enchanted place
called the Hundred Acre Wood.
But of all his animal friends,
Christopher Robin's very best friend
was a bear called Winnie the Pooh.
Winnie the Pooh?
Wait half a darn minute.
It seems to me that most of these stories
are about that silly old bear.
Well, then, Tigger,
who should this story be about?
Well, I happen to know someone
who's extremely fascinatin'.
Not to mention handsome
and debonair-y.
But the title already says
"Winnie the Pooh."
That's easy to fix.
There. Now that's a wonderful title.
And speakin' of wonderful things...
♪ The wonderful thing about Tiggers is
Tiggers are wonderful things ♪
♪ Their tops are made out of rubber
Their bottoms are made out of springs ♪
♪ They're bouncy, trouncy
flouncy, pouncy ♪
♪ Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun ♪
♪ But the most wonderful thing
about Tiggers is ♪
♪ I'm the only one ♪
♪ Tiggers are cuddly fellas
Tiggers are awfully sweet ♪
♪ Everyone el-es is jealous
That's why I repeat and repeat ♪
♪ The wonderful thing about Tiggers is
Tiggers are marvellous chaps ♪
♪ They're loaded with vim and with
vigour, they love to leap in your laps ♪
♪ They're jumpy, bumpy, clumpy, pumpy ♪
♪ Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun ♪
♪ But the most wonderful thing
about Tiggers is ♪
♪ I'm the only one
I'm the only... ♪
Hello. I'm Tigger.
That's T-I-double-geh-er.
And that's me.
I know. You've bounced me
lots and lots of times.
Yeah. Fun, ain't it?
Say, you wanna go bouncin' with me?
On account of bouncin's what
Tiggers do the best.
I'd go bouncing with you,
Tigger, except that I must
count all these honey pots
to be sure that I have enough for winter.
Let me get that, please!
Bother.
What do these Pooh Bears
like about this icky,
sticky stuff anyway?
Well, no time for goofin' off!
I got dawdlin' to do!
T-T-F-N. Ta-ta for now.
Oh, dear, dear...
Hiya, Piglet, ol' pal!
What say you and I
do a little bouncin' together?
Bouncing?
Oh, my. I haven't enough
firewood to last the winter,
-and...
-Why, sure you do.
Why, there's lots of firewood.
It's lyin' all over the place.
-Whoa!
-There! See?
Now we could go bouncin'.
But I would really rather prefer
that my firewood
not have quite so much chair in it.
Well, then... T-T-F-N!
Gotta be bouncin' along.
Well, hello there,
and good mornin', Mrs. Kanga, ma'am!
Well, good morning, Tigger, dear.
She called me "dear."
Pardon me for askin', but
you wouldn't happen to be interested
in doin' a bit of bouncin'
with me, would ya?
Well, I'm afraid I have
just too much to do this morning, dear.
Well, if you have to.
See ya later. Bye.
Tigger, Tigger! Tigger.
I wonder why nobody
wants to bounce with me.
Oh, well, what am I talkin' about?
There's plenty of others
I haven't even asked yet.
And so, the others all came round
to see what they might do to help.
But the end of Eeyore's house
was merely the beginning
of a very unfortunate day.
Wow. Look at the size of it.
Your attention, please.
I have officially completed the plans.
What plans?
The plans. For removing this boulder,
and restoring to Eeyore
his happy home.
No need to bother on my account.
All we need is a little
team effort.
Rabbit's Rock Remover.
Now, then.
Pooh Bear! Release the counterweight!
Kanga and Roo,
start pressurising
the granite extractor.
Piglet!
Piglet, start pulling
your own weight over there.
But I don't weigh anything.
Now, now, a little more over there.
Yes, that's good. No, no, no.
No. More pulling over here.
This way. That's right. All right now.
Oh, good.
-I think...
-Bother.
Oh, my.
Well, now, why didn't it work?
Let's see here now.
The counterweight...
Perhaps we could use
another helping hand.
Yes, all we really need is...
Tigger!
Hello, you blokes!
Anyone up for a little bouncin'?
No! No! No bouncing!
Look! Just look at all
this work we have to do!
What? Movin' that old thing?
Not a problem.
All you need is a little bouncin'.
How will bouncing
move the rock, Tigger?
Tut, tut, tut. Not now, Piglet.
If maybe we had a little...
Right there!
"Bouncing will move this boulder."
It's almost amusing.
Help!
Wow.
Now that that's outta the way,
who's up for a little bouncing?
What is it with you and bouncing?
Just look at my rock remover!
Everything's ruined.
And all you can think about is bouncing!
But that's what Tiggers do best.
Exactly.
Unlike us.
I'm afraid he's right, dear.
What we're trying to say is
that we really can't bounce
like Tiggers, anyway, because...
We're not Tiggers.
Who needs them other fellas anyhow?
♪ Mostly I'm happy and I'm bouncy ♪
♪ Because I am the onliest one ♪
♪ But now all at once I feel so lonely ♪
♪ For someone like me ♪
♪ Someone like me ♪
♪ Right now I'm sorta feeling downcy ♪
♪ I'm just about the loneliest one ♪
♪ And deep in my heart I'm sorta wishin' ♪
♪ For someone like me ♪
♪ Someone like me ♪
♪ Somebody with springs and things ♪
♪ Who laughs and sings ♪
♪ And jumps every day ♪
♪ Somebody who's fun, fun, fun ♪
♪ Who loves to trounce and pounce ♪
♪ And bounce their gloomies away ♪
♪ How I dream there is another
A double ♪
♪ Or a triple of me ♪
♪ To keep him company ♪
♪ But since I'm awake I feel so lonely ♪
♪ Because I know it can't be ♪
♪ It never can be ♪
♪ Bein' that I'm the one and onliest ♪
♪ Someone like me ♪
Tigger?
Don't be sad, Tigger.
Why don't you go bouncing?
That'll cheer you up.
No one to bounce with, Roo Boy.
Well, what about another Tigger?
Another Tigger?
No, it's... It's impossibibble.
It's crazy. I'm the onliest one.
But aren't there other Tiggers?
I've got a mama. Don't you
have a family somewhere, too?
Why, that's...
I mean...
A family full of Tiggers, you say.
Can you imaginate such a thing?
There'd be more Tiggers
than you could stick a shake at!
And we'd all be bouncin'!
Bouncin' mornin',
noon and nighty-night!
But I could still bounce
with you, right, Tigger?
My very own Tigger family!
You wish to find your family.
A most noble quest indeed.
Here we are.
Help yourself to the cream and sugar.
The search for
Familius Genus Tiggeris.
That is Latin, I believe. Or is it Greek?
Speaking of family,
why, my very own family portraits
hang right over there,
a collection I've gathered
throughout the years.
Notice the interesting twists and turns
of its many branches
stretching out across the ages.
It all comes from having
strong roots, you know,
and plenty of time to grow.
In fact, I do believe
that the very seed of my family
began to germinate
as far back as the 14th century
when a great-great-great-grand
Uncle Torbett of mine
went out on a limb
and proclaimed his blossoming love
to a blooming young maid.
As their love blossomed,
they eventually were blessed
with nine fine, young saplings.
Never a bough did break in that...
Oh, my dear boy,
are you quite all right?
Have some more tea.
Anyway, if I may go out on a limb here,
I would first and foremost
suggest for Tigger
that to find one's family,
one must first look up one's family tree.
It does bring to mind
a distant nephew of mine.
A handsome fellow
who became a sailor
and fell in with a member of the feline...
My family tree.
My family tree!
Why didn't I think of thinkin' of that?
So long, Beak Lips! Thanks for the tip!
I say, was it something I said?
And so began Tigger's
grand search for his family tree.
He searched high.
He searched low.
He searched near.
And he searched far.
Yoo-hoo!
Family!
Halloo!
Tigger, how are you gonna know
which tree is your family tree?
Why, that's obvious, Roo Boy.
My Tigger family tree
has got to be the biggest,
hugest and most gigantical tree
in the entire Hundred Acre Woodses
on account of all the enormous,
numerical, numerous numbers
of Tigger family members
that'll be on it.
And besides, and furthermore,
it'll be all stripedy, just like yours truly.
The only question is,
where could my family tree be?
There.
Good as new, or maybe even better,
if I do say so myself.
Could be a bit drafty.
Might leak some.
Sorta lopsided.
Kinda cramped.
Otherwise, a dream house.
Hiya, Donkey Boy!
-Tigger!
Tigger!
Back to his bouncy old self.
Is this perhaps
a Tigger family tree up there?
Were you asking us
to bounce with you?
Because, you see,
we would be glad to...
Halloo! Tigger family!
Halloo!
No, not this one.
-Halloo! Other Tiggers!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are and aren't!
-Come out, come out...
-Et cetera! Halloo!
-Halloo!
-Tigger's family!
Pooh Bear?
I didn't know Tigger had a family.
Yes. Only it appears
that he has lost them.
Seemed to be lookin' for 'em.
Was that something we were
supposed to be doing, too?
Why, I believe it must be, Piglet.
I quite often remember to forget
these sorts of things.
Aren't you coming, Rabbit?
To look for more Tiggers?
As if one wasn't bad enough!
No, no! No! I have too many
winter preparations to make!
And if you three had any sense,
you'd be doing the same.
Come on.
-Hallooo! Hallooo!
-Hallooo!
-Tiggers!
Come out, come out,
wherever you aren't.
-Hallooo! Tiggers!
-Where aren't those Tiggers anyway?
We looked every which and where.
Not to mention right over there.
And not a single stripedy tree in sight.
Maybe I been goin' about this
all the wrong way upside-down.
Maybe what I need to do
is find some sort of clue
as to where are their whereabouts.
What kind of clue?
Maybe in here. Some thingamabob
or an heiry-loom or something.
Maybe this belonged to my uncle!
Whatever. And just think,
if there are other Tiggers,
we could all bounce the
Whoop-de-Dooper, Loop-de-Looper,
Ali-Ooper Bounce! 'Cause it's
the bounce that Tiggers do best.
The Whoop-de-what-do...
What kind of bounce?
You know, that bounce I bounced
when I bounced that big rock.
The most hardest bounce of them all,
that only the very bestest
bouncers can bounce.
Only the very bestest
bouncers can bounce it.
Could my auntie
have made this for me?
I could bounce it.
It looks like she made a pair.
If you could teach me
the Whoopy-Super-Duper Bounce,
-then I could...
-Teach ya the W-D-double-L-A-O-B?
Why... What? That's ridickerous!
It's a very powerful bounce!
And it's only for professional bouncers.
-But I'm a real good bouncer.
-Yeah.
No offence there, Roo Boy,
but I think you're a little
on the smallish side of tiny,
and kinda lackin' in perpendicaler.
I could do the Whooper Dooper...
The Looper Dooper...
If you teach me!
You can't bounce the bounce
if you can't even pronounce the bounce!
Repeat after Tigger.
♪ The Whoop-de-Dooper
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce! ♪
♪ It's got the zip that makes you flip
And that's what really counts! ♪
♪ In the Whoop-de-Dooper
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce! ♪
Now, half this bounce is 90% mental.
If you calculate
the specific Tiggerjectory
of your stripecelleration diviferous
by the square boot of your rebounce,
your vertical situituation indicator
and your stripersonic
springnertia should rikatikachet
your hydranific ful-silly-age
into an accelerometric de-orbit!
Any questions?
When do I get to learn
the Whooping-Looper-Whooper...
I mean, the Ooper-Dooper-Whooper...
♪ The Whoop-de-Dooper
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce ♪
♪ The more you try, the more you fly
And that's what really counts ♪
♪ In the Whoop-de-Dooper
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce ♪
Now, ya swing your legs up high.
And you twist your tail in tight.
Wind up all yer springs
and, with your eyes
fixated straight ahead,
you let it all loose!
Is this right?
♪ It's best when done by Tiggers
'Cause our Tiggerific figgers ♪
♪ Are filled with vims and viggers
And that's the thing that triggers ♪
♪ The Whoop-de-Dooper
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce ♪
Loop-de-Looper Ali-Ooper Bounce ♪
♪ The more you try the more you fly
And that's what really counts ♪
♪ lt activates, it elevates
Accelerates and more ♪
♪ You're bouncin' off the ceiling
Like you never did before! ♪
♪ -The Whoop-de-Dooper
-Whoop-de-Dooper ♪
♪ -Loop-de-Looper
-Loop-de-Looper ♪
♪ Ali-Ooper ♪
♪ Bounce ♪
Wow!
Now me! Now me!
Wait a minute.
We haven't gone over
the safety rules and regularations.
Rule number one.
Always bounce in a well-lit area.
Rule number the-next-one.
Never bounce near an open flame.
Rule three.
Never bounce right after eatin',
-or you'll get tail cramps.
-First you...
Rule number four.
Do not forget rule number three.
-Let it all loose...
-Never bounce when exhausticated.
Rule number seven...
I think you let it a little too loose.
Maybe another lesson?
I could...
What is this doohickey?
No. Why, that's no doohickey.
It's a thingamabob.
Been in the family for generations.
And I never even knew I had it.
This is the exact thingamabob
I was lookin' for.
And it must have a picture
of my Tigger family inside it.
Oh, boy!
I can't wait!
I'll bet I got my mother's eyes.
And my father's tail.
And one of my sisters' chins, of course.
My grandpappy's stripes.
It's kinda... Sorta...
Empty. Completely Tiggerless.
How am I supposed to
find my family now?
Maybe there's
another way to reach 'em.
Another way?
A letter!
Why don't you write 'em a letter?
-Halloo!
-Hello?
-Halloo out there!
-Hello? Tigger's family?
-Tigger's family tree!
-Hello!
How will we know a Tigger
family member when we see one?
I suspect that he, or she,
would be rather more bouncy
than usual, Piglet.
I found 'em. Tigger's family.
-Really?
-Well, Eeyore.
Here they are. Bouncin' like anything.
Stripes and all.
No need to thank me.
Do these particular Tiggers seem
rather strange to you, Piglet?
Yes, and rather fierce.
Still, I suppose you never
can tell with Tiggers.
Pardon me, Mr. or Mrs. Tigger.
But could you, perhaps,
accompany me back to Tigger's house?
He misses you very much, you see.
And he... Oh, bother.
Hello, Tigger family member.
I was wondering, that is,
if you're not too busy to...
Whoa! Dear.
Sinkin'? Figures.
If I could just have a moment.
Please, come back!
We really need your help.
It would just take a minute! Oh, bother.
Nice Tigger.
I don't remember Tiggers
being quite this slippery!
-Do you, Pooh?
-Well, now that I think of it,
I don't remember a Tigger making
quite that sort of sound, either.
-Piglet?
-Yes, Pooh Bear?
I don't think these are
the right sort of Tiggers after all.
Not that anyone'll miss me.
Let me see, now.
"Dear T-I-double-geh-ers... Tiggers.
"Greetin's and salivatin's.
"Please drop by any ol' time
"on account of my house is your house,
"and vicey-versey. Love, Tigger!"
There. That oughta do it.
Now there's nothing to do
but wait.
-Hello, Tigger's family.
-Hello?
-Tigger's family?
-Hallo? Are you up there?
Anybody out there?
Why, if my tummy is not mistaken,
this particular family tree
is a bee sort of family tree.
And where there are bees,
there's honey.
I think there may be
something moving in this tree.
Do you think it could be
Tigger's family up there, Pooh Bear?
I suppose there's only one way
to find out, Piglet.
Just as my tummy suspected.
Bother.
If only these bees were a bit less busy.
Perhaps if I hummed
a soothing sort of song,
♪ like such. ♪
♪ Go to sleep... Quiet ♪
♪ If you're a bee ♪
♪ Lullaby ♪
♪ Lullabee, lullabee ♪
♪ Honey bees in the tree ♪
♪ Rest your wings ♪
♪ Till the morning light ♪
♪ Lullabee, lullabee ♪
♪ Honey bees in the tree ♪
♪ Your honey ♪
♪ Is safe tonight ♪
♪ Just dream to the tune
I am singing ♪
♪ Time to stop
All that buzzing ♪
♪ And stinging ♪
♪ Lullabee, lullabee ♪
♪ Honey bees in the tree ♪
♪ All I want is a smackrel ♪
♪ Or two ♪
♪ Or three ♪
♪ Don't sleep lightly ♪
♪ Sleep very tightly ♪
♪ Happy slumbers ♪
♪ To you ♪
Pooh Bear's been up in that tree
an awful long time,
don't you think?
Most likely he's stuck.
Been known to happen.
Oh, dear.
Then, I better climb up
and see if he's all right.
Pooh Bear, are you stuck?
Oh, bother.
Pooh Bear?
-Piglet?
-Yes, Pooh?
I have come to the conclusion
that these bees are definitely
not the right sorts of Tiggers.
It doesn't look good.
Bees! Run!
At last, the day had come to an end,
as days often will.
And what had begun
as a very exciting idea
had changed
to a rather discouraging one.
Tigger?
I gotta go home now.
Mama will be worried about me.
Tigger?
What, am I kiddin' myself?
They're not comin'.
'Cause I might as well face it.
There aren't any other Tiggers.
And, I guess that means
this silly old thing's
just gonna stay empty for all of forever.
But isn't that the wonderful
thing about Tiggers?
-Bein' the only one?
-You betcha, Roo Boy.
Oh, the most wonderful thing
about Tiggers is I'm...
The very only,
last, lonely,
single, solitary
one.
First, I...
And, just so...
And then I...
Like this.
And then a little twist, like such.
And then I let it all loose, with a...
Whatever are you doing, Roo dear?
I'm practising the
Whoop-de-Doop-tee Bounce.
Maybe, if I do it really good for Tigger,
he wouldn't miss not
having a family so much.
But I can't bounce it yet.
Well, I'm sure you'll be able
to do it in time, dear.
But Tigger seems awful lonely,
don't you think, Mama?
I suppose he might be,
every now and again.
-Mama?
-Yes, dear?
I wish I had a big brother like Tigger.
Now, why wish that when
you have a Tigger like Tigger?
'Cause then I'd be his little brother.
And he'd be just like one of our family.
-Wouldn't that be great?
-But, Roo, dear,
Tigger is one of our family.
And, as long as we care for him,
he always will be.
Sweet dreams, Roo, dear.
I still wish I could do
something to make him feel better.
I say, young Roo,
if you suggest that a letter'll
bring cheer to our friend Tigger,
then we shall, by all means, write one.
Now, what sort of letter is this to be?
It's by us, from them, to him.
By which from what to whom?
From Tigger's family to Tigger.
Yes.
"Dear Tigger. Just a note to say..."
"Just a note to say..."
What shall it say?
Well...
I suppose it might say,
"Dress warmly?"
I see. Excellent advice.
Owl?
Perhaps, "Eat well?"
Good point, Pooh Bear.
"Stay safe and sound?"
A very good idea, Piglet.
"Keep smilin'."
"We're always there for you."
"Wishing you all the best,
signed, your family."
-There.
-Won't Tigger be pleased?
-How wonderful for Tigger!
-What a splendid idea, Roo.
-Nice sentiment.
-Marvellous work, everyone.
And so, the next morning...
Hello, everybody!
Pooh Boy!
Piglet!
Kanga! Kanga! Roo! Roo! Roo!
Eeyore! Eeyore, old buddy!
Look at what I got! A letter!
A letter for me, that's who!
T-I-double-geh-er spells Tigger!
I wonder who it might be from?
From my very own family.
I knew I had one!
A great, big family!
Full of uncles and aunties
and grand-Tiggers!
And second cousin Tiggers!
And they're all just like me!
Just imaginate it.
Hundreds of thousands of Tiggers!
All bouncin' around up there,
in our huge, gigantical family tree!
♪ There's momsey Tiggers ♪
♪ And popsey Tiggers ♪
♪ And Tiggers I never knew ♪
♪ Like sister Tiggers
And brother Tiggers ♪
♪ And cousin Tiggers, too ♪
♪ There's grandma Tiggers
And grandpa Tiggers ♪
♪ As you can plainly see ♪
♪ When we're all together
It's a jumpin' jamboree ♪
♪ Round, round my family tree ♪
♪ I look like them
and they look like me ♪
♪ Round, round my family tree
We're a happy family ♪
♪ There's huge slews of nephew Tiggers ♪
♪ Uncle Tiggers by the ton ♪
♪ Whippersnappin'
great-great-grandpappy Tiggers ♪
♪ And grandma Tiggers are fun ♪
♪ Skinny, tiny, thin little Tiggers ♪
♪ And roly-poly Tiggers, too ♪
♪ But we're all relations
And we're quite a mighty crew ♪
♪ Round, round my family tree ♪
♪ I look like them and they look like me ♪
♪ The amazing Flying Tiggers! ♪
♪ Round, round my family tree
We're a happy family ♪
♪ The firstest-most roots
Of my family tree ♪
♪ Reach way back in history ♪
♪ To the braverest fiercerest ♪
♪ Noblerest Tiggers
You'd ever care to see ♪
♪ The heroicest figgers
Of my ancestor Tiggers ♪
♪ Have always been hailed and cheered ♪
♪ And the sculpturous grace
Of our Tiggerous faces ♪
♪ Is why we're all revered ♪
♪ There were warrior Tiggers ♪
♪ Explorier Tiggers ♪
♪ And Tiggers of worldly acclaim ♪
♪ There were glorious
Phantasmagorious Tiggers ♪
♪ With prizes and fortunes and fame ♪
♪ There's the glamorous branch
And the amorous branch ♪
♪ Of our fabulous family tree ♪
♪ And when we sing together ♪
♪ -We're in...
-Perfect harmony ♪
♪ Round and round my family tree ♪
♪ I look like them and they look like me ♪
♪ We're a happy family ♪
♪ There's momsey Tiggers ♪
♪ And popsey Tiggers ♪
♪ And Tiggers I never knew ♪
♪ Like uncle Tiggers ♪
♪ And nephew Tiggers ♪
♪ And grandma Tiggers, too ♪
♪ And when we Tiggers all get together ♪
♪ We really have a ball! ♪
♪ The bounciest ♪
♪ Trounciest, flounciest
Pounciest ♪
♪ Most Tiggerificest ♪
♪ Family reunion of all! ♪
Everybody bounce.
You know how to do it!
And I'm especially excited
about this part.
They miss me somethin' awful,
and they're comin' to see me!
Tomorrow!
Tomorrow?
Tigger, I can't wait to meet them.
Now, where did it say that, exactly?
Exackatackly nowhere, per se,
'cause with us Tiggers,
you gotta read betwixt the lines.
I'm gonna see my whole family,
'cause my whole family
is all comin' to see
little ol' you-know-who!
But the most wonderful thing
about Tiggers is
I'm not the only one!
Now, Tigger was
so enormously excited
that his friends couldn't help but feel,
well, a bit concerned.
Tigger?
-Hiya, Roo!
-What are you doin', Tigger?
Why, I'm buildin'
a family room onto my house,
so my family will have plenty of room.
They gotta live somewheres after
the big family reunitin' party.
-Party?
-Why, sure!
Boy, it's gonna be great.
It's all right in my letter.
Speakin' of which,
you wanna hear me read it
once or thrice again?
-Tigger...
-"Dear..."
They call me "dear."
It's embarrassing, ain't it?
The way us Tiggers go oozin'
oodles and doodles of affection.
-Yeah, but...
-"Dear Tigger." Ya see that?
Us Tiggers always call us
Tiggers by their firstest names.
"Dress warmly."
They're worried sick about me.
"Eat well. Keep smilin'.
Stay safe and sound."
And here is the best part of all.
"We're always there for ya."
Isn't this the all-time greatest?
Yeah, the greatest.
I was gonna tell him, but I couldn't.
Pooh, do you think you could?
Why, certainly, Roo.
Could what?
Tell him about the letter?
Why, certainly.
Could that be them already?
Tiggers are usually
fashionabubbly late.
Welcome, dear brothers,
to the house of Tigger.
Hiya, buddy bear.
Just in time to help me finish up
with the finishin' up.
Hold these while I put those there.
Tigger, there was
a very important matter,
which I must discuss.
You're right, Pooh Boy!
I could use another balloon
or two dozen!
Tigger.
Somethin' isn't right here.
Much better.
Now, what'd you wanna talk about,
Pooh Boy? Pooh?
Perhaps I'll need a bit of help.
Tigger was so very excited,
and had so very many things to do,
he heard very little
of what anyone else was saying.
But as it so happened,
none of his friends had the heart
to tell Tigger very much
of anything, anyway.
Not like he won't find out for himself
sooner or later.
The poor dear.
He'll be so disappointed.
Dear.
Indeed. What have we done?
Or, perhaps his family will come,
and everything will be fine.
That's it!
There! A veritable work of art.
And just how will this cheer up Tigger?
Well, the stripes look okay.
But what we have to do
is act real Tiggery.
We gotta do a lot of bouncin'
and say a lot of Tigger stuff.
Such as, "Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo."
"Absoposilutely?"
That's kinda, sorta like Tigger, but...
♪ How to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger is up to you ♪
♪ You've got to look like a Tigger ♪
♪ And sound like a Tigger ♪
♪ And act like a Tigger, too ♪
♪ If we paint black stripes
On our underwear ♪
♪ And glue on whiskers, too ♪
♪ We're bound to appear
Far more as Tiggers do ♪
Unquestionably.
♪ Maybe we could all say, "T-T-F-N" ♪
♪ And shout, "Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo" ♪
♪ We all might sound
A lot more Tiggerish, too ♪
Do you think?
♪ And that is how to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger is up to you ♪
♪ You've got to look like a Tigger
Sound like a Tigger ♪
♪ And act like a Tigger, too ♪
♪ If we break things up
And knock things down ♪
♪ And leave the place a mess ♪
♪ That's the thing that
Tigger does the best ♪
♪ I oughta know. ♪
♪ And if I don't eat honey ♪
♪ From the honey pot ♪
♪ Ol' Tigger will plainly see ♪
♪ I must be another Tigger ♪
♪ Because I couldn't possibly be me ♪
♪ And that is how to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger
How to be a Tigger is up to you ♪
♪ You've got to look like a Tigger
And sound like a Tigger ♪
♪ And act like a Tigger... ♪
Also.
Thank goodness I found you all here.
There's a terrible storm headed for...
What on earth are you doing?
Stripes? Springs?
Have you lost your minds?
You should be covering windows,
counting your supplies,
gathering firewood!
Winter is here
and you aren't even ready.
What are you doing
wasting your time with...
What am I doing wasting my time?
I've got serious work to do!
At least I haven't lost sight
of what's really important.
Well, I really didn't have enough time
to gather any firewood.
I am down to this last, lonely honey pot.
Well, come to think of it,
we don't really look or act
very much like Tiggers.
Thought I was pretty convincing.
Wait! Wait!
We gotta do it! We have to do it!
Think how sad Tigger's gonna feel.
Well, we don't really know
how to be a Tigger.
Yeah, we do.
♪ If we could all be happy ♪
♪ Full of friendliness and cheer ♪
♪ He'll surely see
we are his family ♪
♪ We're filled with joy
and laughter ♪
♪ And the happiness he starts ♪
♪ And feel it from
the bottom of our hearts ♪
♪ And that is how to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger is up to you ♪
♪ You've got to be like a Tigger ♪
♪ Full of glee like a Tigger ♪
♪ With a happy... ♪
♪ -How to be a Tigger
-How to be a Tigger ♪
♪ How to be a Tigger
is up to you ♪
♪ You've got to be like a Tigger ♪
♪ Full of glee like a Tigger ♪
♪ With a happy
hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo ♪
I wonder where they could be.
What if they got the wrong directions?
What if they strayed
off the beaten path?
What if they're out there,
hopelessly lost?
Clutched in the cruel grapst of winter?
Hold on, Tiggers, I'm coming to get ya!
Surprise!
Is it? Is it?
Is it really you?
My very own, one and only family?
Come in. Come in. Come in.
Lots of catchin' uppin' we gotta do!
We haven't seen each other in...
We haven't seen each other!
Gee, it's nice to have
all us Tiggers
gettin' together like this. Huh?
-Oh, yes, yes.
-It certainly is.
What am I... Where the heck
are my mannerisms?
Refreshin' refreshyments
for all, comin' right up!
Help yourself. Don't be shy.
Here you go! Take two, you're small.
I mean, they're small. Have another.
-Lot of vitamins and minerals...
-Bother.
My, what a nice home you have.
Yes, and what lovely decorations.
So bouncety and stripedy.
Nice weather.
Party flavour?
Now this party's really startin'
to pick up.
So what you been up to, cousin?
I've been...
Bouncin'. Bouncin', bouncin'!
Mornin' and noon, and noon to night.
Why, that's what I been doin', too!
It must run in the family. Hey!
Who's up for some
family-type fun and games?
You look like a fun-lovin' type of fella.
I got a great party-type,
family-type game we can play!
How about "Pin the tail on the..."
It looks like you already been playin' it.
Phew!
I know.
Let's all do what Tiggers do best!
That would be bouncin', of course.
-Of course! Bouncing!
-Absoposilutely.
-Yeah!
-Let the bouncin' begin!
Yeah!
Bounce, bounce.
I do enjoy bouncing!
Don't bounce too high,
now, Roo... Tigger.
Tigger, dear.
You certainly have
a wonderful family, Tigger.
Wait a second!
We gotta bounce
the Whoop-de-Dooper,
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce!
What a Tiggerific idea!
Guests first.
Ya gotta swing your legs up high.
And ya twist yer tail in tight.
Ya wind up all yer springs.
And, with your eyes fixed
straight ahead,
ya let it all loose with a...
Roo, what are you doin'
impersonisin' a Tigger?
Piglet?
Kanga.
Owl. Eeyore!
We only wanted to help, Tigger.
Now I understand. It was all a big joke.
Well, that's all right.
'Cause somewhere out there,
there's a Tigger family tree
full of my real Tigger family.
I got a letter to prove it!
And I'm gonna find 'em.
So, T-T-F-E.
Ta-ta forever!
Poor Tigger. All alone in the cold.
He must be very sad, and perhaps lost.
And maybe even a bit...
...hungry.
Bother.
Pooh, you gotta help me find Tigger.
It's all my fault.
He never would've left
if it wasn't 'cause of me.
I didn't mean to make him feel bad.
I just... I just wanted him
to be my big brother.
We gotta go find him! We just gotta.
And so we will.
What we need is...
Think, think, think.
-An expotition.
-An expotition?
Yes! To the place
where Tigger is. Or was.
Or will be.
-I believe Rabbit should lead us.
-Rabbit?
Oh, yes.
He's the only one who ever says
he knows what he's doing.
Absolutely not.
I mean, well, after all, he...
It was not my...
He wanted to leave. Didn't he?
But, Rabbit...
He could always give that
extra little push when you needed it.
Thank you, Roo.
It was nice to have him near
when things were frightful.
Sorta lit up the room when he came in.
Well, you... What do you need me for?
Why don't you go find him yourselves?
But we're just not
clever enough, Rabbit.
Rabbit? I miss him.
Well, I...
Very well.
Tigger!
-Tigger!
Now, now, careful, everyone.
It's a bit windy!
Are you all right, Eeyore? Eeyore?
Oh, dear.
-Help!
-We must take care to stick together.
Perhaps not this stuck, Piglet.
Pardon me, Pooh.
-Tigger!
-Tigger! Tigger!
-Tigger?
Tiggers!
Where are ya, Tiggerseses?
I hope they're all okay.
Tiggers!
Whoa! Whoa!
The biggest, hugest,
and most gigantical stripedy tree
in all the entire
Hundred Acre Woodses!
Is it? Is it?
My family tree!
I found it! I found it! I can't believe it!
Halloo! Halloo up there!
Where are ya, Tiggers? It's me, Tigger!
Halloo!
Halloo, family!
I got your letter, and I came to see ya.
Halloo!
Hallo?
Maybe they forgot I was comin'.
But I thought...
I thought you were always there for me.
Tigger!
-Where are you, Tigger?
-Tigger!
-Thank...
-Oh, you're welcome.
Tigger?
"Dear Tigger."
Tigger, is that you?
Tigger!
Tigger! It's me, Roo!
-Down here!
-Oh, Tigger! Thank goodness!
-Tigger!
What? Hello? Did...
Could it be?
Look down here! We were worried!
It looks like the whole family
is finally here!
I'm coming, Tiggers!
Tiggers! Tiggers!
-Hey, you're not Tiggers.
-It's so wonderful to see you.
What are you guyses doing here?
Doing? What are we doing here?
We came all this way to look for you!
Now, forget about all this other
Tiggers nonsense and come home.
Nonsense?
No!
No! No! No! No...
Are you... Are you crazy?
It's not safe out here.
Exactakly! That's why
you should all go home.
Where it is safe.
But I've gotta wait here,
in my family tree, for my real family!
Family! Family! Family! Family! Family!
Is that a rumbly in your tumbly, Pooh?
I don't think so, Piglet.
Come on. Hurry it up!
No time for dawdlin'.
Not a second to waste.
Watch yourself there, Roo Boy.
Take care, Pooh Bear.
Don't be scared, Piglet.
Up ya go, Donkey Boy!
Oh, help!
Tigger!
Oh, no!
The Whoop-de-Dooper
Loop-de-Looper, Ali-Ooper Bounce!
The more you try, the more you fly.
And that's what really counts!
Tigger! Tigger!
Wake up, Tigger! Wake up!
Tigger?
-Oh, we're saved!
-Hooray!
-You saved him. You saved him.
-That was just wonderful, Roo.
-Roo, that was very brave.
-What a Whoop-de-Doopin',
Loop-de-Loopin', Ali-Oopin' Bounce
that was!
It was, wasn't it?
I mean, I really did it, didn't I?
Did ya?
Come here, you!
Why that bounce was just
as good as any old Tigger...
Tigger family member.
Tigger?
Please don't go.
There they are!
We found them! We found them!
-There's Tigger!
-Roo!
-Mama! Mama!
-Oh, Roo,
we've been searching all over for you.
Oh, Roo, dear, I was so worried.
I'm sorry, Mama. I'm all right.
-Oh, my little Roo.
-Pooh Bear!
-Christopher Robin.
Pooh Bear! Pooh!
There you are!
-Silly old bear.
-Oh, my!
-Christopher Robin!
-Nice to see you.
Where have you all been?
We were looking for Tigger
looking for Tigger's family.
Tigger's family?
You didn't have to go looking for them.
But I got a letter and it said that...
That... It was right...
I musta lost it in the avalanchee.
I can't even remember the words.
"Dear Tigger. Just a note to say..."
-"Dress warmly."
-"Eat well."
"Stay safe and sound."
-"Keep smilin'."
-"We're always there for you."
"Signed..."
"Your family."
You mean, you fellas are my family?
I'm afraid we have
nothing better to offer.
Well, of course not, Pooh Boy.
'Cause there's nothin' better
than the best!
I shoulda seen it all along.
Spotted you a mile away!
Oh, it was very frightening.
And then the whole mountain came
down on top of us, but Tigger saved us.
I wasn't worried at all.
Except for the part
where I was worried, of course.
Ahem, ahoom and et cetera.
In honour of this most
occasional occasion,
my firstest ever family reunitin',
I'd like to present
each of ya with a present.
Firstest, for Eeyore,
a new family room
for your lovely home.
Seems kinda big.
Bit on the comfy side. Not very drafty.
But I suppose I'll get used to it.
-I love parties.
-How wonderful!
Lovely party, isn't it?
And for Pooh Boy,
enough honey to last all winter!
Or till next Thursday, anyways.
Why, thank you, Tigger.
It looks good enough to eat.
And for Piglet, ol' pal,
a winter's worth of firewood.
Keep warm.
-Oh, thank you, Tigger!
-You're very welcome.
I picked out each piece myself.
And, for you, Long Ears,
I promise, from now on, I'll
always watch where I'm bouncin'.
Oh, thank you, Tigger.
Bravo, Tigger! Bravo, I say.
-Very well done indeed.
-I'm very impressed.
-Thank you so much!
-Thank you so much, Tigger.
Look at this!
Whoa!
You didn't think I was gonna
disremember you, did ya?
Go on, go on. Open 'er up!
It's all yours.
Is it really for me, Tigger?
Only the best
for my bestest little brother.
Wait half a minute.
We still need a family
portrait to put in it.
Look this way, everybody. Closer.
Smile.
♪ Sunny days and starry nights ♪
♪ And lazy afternoons ♪
♪ You're countin'
castles in the clouds ♪
♪ And hummin' little tunes ♪
♪ But somehow
right before your eyes ♪
♪ The summer fades away ♪
♪ Everything is different ♪
♪ And everything has changed ♪
♪ If you feel lost ♪
♪ And on your own ♪
♪ And far from home ♪
♪ You're never alone, you know ♪
♪ Just think of your friends ♪
♪ The ones who care ♪
♪ They all will be
waitin' there ♪
♪ With love to share ♪
♪ And your heart will lead you ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ Funny how a photograph ♪
♪ Can take you back in time ♪
♪ To places and embraces ♪
♪ That you thought
you'd left behind ♪
♪ But tryin' to remind you ♪
♪ That you're not the only one ♪
♪ That no one is an island ♪
♪ When all is said and done ♪
♪ If you feel lost ♪
♪ And on your own ♪
♪ And far from home ♪
♪ You're never alone, you know ♪
♪ Just think of your friends ♪
♪ The ones who care ♪
♪ They all will be
waitin' there ♪
♪ With love to share ♪
♪ And your heart will lead you ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ There'll come a day
when you're losin' your way ♪
♪ And you won't know where ♪
♪ You belong ♪
♪ They say that home
is where the heart is ♪
♪ So follow your heart ♪
♪ And know that
you can't go wrong ♪
♪ If you feel lost
and on your own ♪
♪ And far from home ♪
♪ You're never alone, you know § ♪
♪ Just think of your friends ♪
♪ The ones who care ♪
♪ They all will be
waitin' there ♪
♪ With love to share ♪
♪ And your heart will lead you ♪
♪ Lost and on your own ♪
♪ And far from home ♪
♪ You're never alone, you know ♪
♪ Just think of your friends ♪
♪ The ones who care ♪
♪ They all will be
waitin' there ♪
♪ With love to share ♪
♪ And your heart will lead you ♪
♪ Where you belong ♪
♪ I know your heart ♪
♪ Will lead you ♪
♪ Home ♪